Guide to the News Service subject files, 1930-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
News Service subject files 1930-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. News Service.
117 linear feet Extent: 117,000 Items
The mission of the Duke News Service is to inform the public and the university community about research, programs, and events at Duke; to increase public understanding and appreciation of scholarly contributions made by Duke's faculty and the work of its other employees and students; and to provide media relations and consultative services to faculty and administrators. Subject-related files created by the Duke University News Service containing clippings, speeches, photographs and reference material.
UA.27.01.0002
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The News Service subject files were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1991-1997, 2002.
Historical Note
The mission of the Duke News Service is to inform the public and the university community about research, programs, and events at Duke; to increase public understanding and appreciation of scholarly contributions made by Duke's faculty and the work of its other employees and students; and to provide media relations and consultative services to faculty and administrators. The Duke News Service works closely with local, national, and international news media, including newspapers, radio and television, magazines, wire services and syndicates.
Collection Overview
The collection is arranged in the following series: General; Blackburn Literary Festival and British American Festival; MedCenter; Richard Nixon; Scrapbook Articles. Within each series the subject files are arranged alphabetically by accession.
Related Material
News Service press releases and clippings.
Duke University Archives.
News Service Biographical Files, 1960-2004.
Duke University Archives.
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - A.B.C (A Better Chance), pre-1975 (Box 1)
  - Academic Council (Box 1)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 1)
  - Accounting, 1941-1970 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, 1956-1967 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, 1968-1976 (Box 1)
  - Aesthetics, Art, Music, 1959 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Aesthetics, Society, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Aircade- Chamber of Commerce (Box 1)
  - Airforce ROTC, to 1966 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Allergy Meet, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Phi Omega (Box 1)
  - Alumnae Weekend, 1950-1968 (Box 1)
  - Alumni General, 1939-1949 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Alumni, 1949-1952 (Box 1)
  - Alumni, 1952-1954 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Alumni, 1954-1959 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Alumni, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Alumni, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, 1966-1967 (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Alumni, 1969 (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Alumni, General, through 1975 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, General, A-J, 1977-1980 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, General, K-Z, 1977-1980 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, General (Box 2)
  - Alumni Council Meet, January, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Day, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Alumni, Individuals, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Service (Box 2)
  - Alumni Rally (Box 2)
  - Alumnus Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
  - Alumnus Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1969- (Box 3)
  - Ambassadors Dance Orchestra (Box 3)
  - American Assembly Conference, 1959-1967 (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1960-1972 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Women, 1962-1974 (Box 3)
  - American College Public Relations Association, 1963-1972 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1977 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1978 (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1979 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1980 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1981 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1982 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1983 (Box 3)
  - American Dance Festival, 1984 (Box 4)
  - American Dance Festival, 1985 (Box 4)
  - American Musical Theater Center, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Angier B. Duke Scholarship (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Annual Fund, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Anthropology, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Apocrypha, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Archive Festival April, 1972-1976 (Box 4)
  - Archives, 1972, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Army Finance School (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Armed Forces Day (Box 4)
  - Army Research (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Army Research Office, 1965-1978 (Box 4)
  - Art, prior to 1960 (Box 5)
  - Art, 1960-1965 (Box 5)
  - Art, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Art Mace and Chain of Office (Box 5)
  - Arts Festival, pre-1975 (Box 5)
  - Art Museum, 1967-1975 (Box 5)
  - Art Museum, 1970-1974 (Box 5)
  - Art Museum, 1970-1977 (Box 5)
  - Artist in Residence, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Artist's Series (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Artist's Series (7 folders) (Box 6)
  - Arts Council (Box 6)
  - A.S.P.U. January, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Athletic Council, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Athletics, 1970-1971 December (Box 6)
  - Athletics, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Athletics, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Athletics General, M.L.King Games, College Football (Box 6)
  - Auxiliary D.U. Hospital (Box 6)
  - Awards, 1970-1976 (Box 6)
  - Band (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1961-1972 (Box 7)
  - Beauty Contestants, to 1965 (Box 7)
  - Biblical Scrolls, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Biddle Mary Duke Foundation (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Biochemistry (Box 7)
  - Biology (Box 7)
  - Biomedical Engineering (Box 7)
  - Black Studies (includes Afro-American Society) (Box 7)
  - Book Reviews (Box 7)
  - Botany Dept. (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Bowl Discussion, 1952 (Box 8)
  - Boys' Club Fund (Box 8)
  - Boycott Bus. Duke Power, 1949 (Box 8)
  - Boy Scout Comporee and Circus, 1952 (Box 8)
  - Brewer-Burch Affair, 1962-1964 (Box 8)
  - Brown, General George S., Anti-Semitism, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
  - Broadway at Duke (Box 8)
  - Buildings, 1930-1960 (Box 8)
  - Buildings Typewritten Stories and Pictures, pre-1961 (Box 8)
  - Buildings, 1960-1963 (Box 8)
  - Buildings, 1964-1973 (Box 9)
  - Buildings, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Buildings, General (Box 9)
  - Business School, 1969-1975 (Box 9)
  - Business School, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
  - Campus Security (Box 9)
  - Canadian Studies, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
  - Career Day, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Careers in Industry (Box 9)
  - Centennial (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Center for Continuing Education, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Center for Southern Studies (Box 9)
  - Chamber Arts Society (Box 10)
  - Chamber Orchestra (Box 10)
  - Chapel, 1932-1952 (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Chapel, 1953-1961 (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Chapel, 1961-1963 (Box 10)
  - Chapel, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
  - Cheating, 1950 1974 (Box 10)
  - Chaplain's Workshop (Box 10)
  - Chemistry (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Chemistry (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - China Trip, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Choral Activities, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Christian Convocation and Pastor's School, 1966-1968, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Christian Convocation (Box 11)
  - The Chronicle (Box 11)
  - Church-Related Activities (Box 11)
  - Circle K Club, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
  - Civil Defense (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - "Civitan Building," 1971 (Box 11)
  - Classical Studies (Box 11)
  - Clinics, Divinity School (Box 11)
  - Coastal Briefing and Related Articles, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Cold Springs Harbor Lab of Quantitative Biology, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Commencement, 1932-1937 (Box 11)
  - Commencement, 1938-1939 (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Commencement, 1940-1942 (Box 11)
  - Commencement, 1943 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1944 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1945 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1946-1948 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1949 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1952 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1953 (Box 12)
  - Commencement, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1957 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1959 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1960 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1962 (Box 13)
  - Commencement Chronological (Box 13)
  - Commencement, 1962 (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1966 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1975 (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1976 (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1977 (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Commonwealth Studies Center, 1971-1973 (Box 15)
  - Communism at Duke and UNC, 1953 (Box 16)
  - Comparative Studies on Southern Africa, 1970-1974 (Box 16)
  - Computation Center (Box 16)
  - Computer Science, 1962-1976 (Box 16)
  - Computer Seminar Impact of Computers on Society, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Concerts and Plays (Box 16)
  - Conferences and Seminars (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Conference, National Science Editors and Writers (Box 16)
  - Continuing Education, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Continuing Education, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Convocation Mat Pictures, Clippings, 1948-1961 (Box 16)
  - Convocation Lectures, Stories, 1948-1962 (Box 16)
  - Convocation General (Box 16)
  - Convocation, 1962-1971 (Box 17)
  - Convocation 1975 Pastor's School Gray Lectures (Box 17)
  - Cooperative Program Duke-UNC in East Asian Studies (Box 17)
  - Cooperative Programs Duke-NCCU (Box 17)
  - Counseling Center, 1952-1975 (Box 17)
  - Crime (Box 17)
  - Curriculum (Box 17)
  - Dad's Day (Box 17)
  - Dateline Duke, 1970 February (Box 17)
  - Dean's List (Box 17)
  - Debate Team (Box 17)
  - Defense, 1941-1942 (Box 17)
  - Development Program (Box 17)
  - DiCecco-Kitchen Duo, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Dietetic Programs (Box 17)
  - Dieticians (Box 17)
  - Dining Hall (Box 17)
  - Distinguished Professorships (Box 17)
  - Divinity School, 1939-1947 (Box 17)
  - Divinity School, 1948-1953 (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Divinity School, 1954-1959 (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Divinity School, 1960-1962 (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Divinity School, 1963 (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Divinity School, 1964-1965 (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Divinity School, 1965-1967 (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Divinity School, 1968-1970 (Box 19)
  - Divinity School, 1970-1972 (Box 19)
  - Divinity School, 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Divinity School, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Divinity School, 1977-1979 (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Dramatics (Box 19)
  - Driver Evaluation, Research, and Education RTP, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Drugs (Box 19)
  - Duke Band, 1970-1976 (Box 19)
  - Duke Chapel, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Duke Cooperative (Box 19)
  - Duke Credit Union, 1969-1977 (Box 19)
  - Duke Dance Program, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Duke Endowment (5 folders) (Box 20)
  - Duke Family (3 folders) (Box 20)
  - Duke University, 1935-1946 (Box 20)
  - Duke University, 1948-1953 (Box 21)
  - Duke University, 1953-1955 (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Duke University, 1955-1957 (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Duke University, 1958 (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Duke University 1959 (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Duke University, 1959-1961 (Box 22)
  - Duke University, 1961-1963 (Box 22)
  - Duke University, 1962 (Box 22)
  - Duke University, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Duke University, 1964-1972 (2 of 3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Duke University, 1964-1972 (3 of 3 folders) (Box 23)
  - Duke University, 1966-1967 (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Duke University, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Duke University, 1969-1972 (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Duke University, 1972-1974 (Box 23)
  - Duke University, circa 1960-1972 (Box 23)
  - Duke University, 1930s-1950s (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - Duke University, 1971 November-1972 May (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1972 June-October (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1973 January-March (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1973 April-June 1973 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1973 July-August 1973 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1973 September-December (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1974 January-May (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1974 June-December (Box 24)
  - Duke University Power Rate Increase, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1980 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1982 (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Duke University Historical Data (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Duke Homestead (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Duke in the News, 1966 May-October; 1967 January-December; 1968 January-December (Box 25)
  - Duke, James B. (Box 25)
  - Duke Players, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Duke Players (4 folders) (Box 25)
  - Duke University Press (7 folders) (Box 26)
  - Duke Songs (Box 26)
  - Duke Traditions (Box 26)
  - Duke's 50th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Durham Legal Aid Office, 1971-1975 (Box 26)
  - Eastward Construction (Box 27)
  - Eastward Dedication (Box 27)
  - Eastward, 1965 (Box 27)
  - Eastward, 1966-1973 (Box 27)
  - Economics, 1938-1965 (Box 27)
  - Economics, 1968-1974 (Box 27)
  - Economics, 1971-1976 (Box 27)
  - Edgemont Community Center (Box 27)
  - Editorials, 1955-1962 (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Editorials, 1963-1965 (1 of 2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Editorials, 1963-1965 (2 of 2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Editorials, 1966-1968 (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Editorials, 1968 September-1970 December (Box 28)
  - Editorials, 1971-1974 (Box 28)
  - Editorials, 1974 (Box 28)
  - Editorials, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
  - Education (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Education, 1963-1974 (1 of 2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Education, 1963-1974 (2 of 2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Education, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - Education, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - Education Improvement Program (Box 29)
  - Educom D.W.C. Anlyan, Chairman (Box 29)
  - Employees Council, 1969 (Box 29)
  - Employee Relations (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Endowment (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Engineering, 1934-1949 (Box 29)
  - Engineering, 1949-1958 (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Engineering 1959-1961 (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Engineering 1963-1966 (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Engineering, 1966-1968 (Box 30)
  - Engineering, 1969-1974 (Box 30)
  - Engineering, 1975 (Box 30)
  - English (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - English, 1966-1975 (Box 30)
  - English Teachers Institute (Box 30)
  - Enrollment (Box 30)
  - Entertainment, 1964 (Box 30)
  - Environmental Forum (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Environmental Health Care (Box 31)
  - Environmental Programs, 1972-1975 (Box 31)
  - Episcopal Student Center (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Epoch Campaign, 1974 (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 31)
  - Faculty Clippings (4 folders) (Box 31)
  - Faculty Clippings, Appointments, Promotions (Box 31)
  - Faculty Club (Box 31)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes FCA (Box 31)
  - Fellowships (Box 31)
  - Fifth Decade (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Film Society (Box 32)
  - Flag Raising Ceremony (Box 32)
  - Flentrop Organ Background (Box 32)
  - Folk-Festival (Box 32)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 32)
  - Foreign Clippings (Box 32)
  - Foreign Students, to 1965 (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Foreign Students, 1970-1979 (Box 32)
  - Forestry, 1936-1961 (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Forestry, 1962-1965 (Box 32)
  - Forestry, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
  - Forestry, 1969-1974 (Box 32)
  - Forestry, 1975-1976 (Box 32)
  - Forestry, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
  - Forestry (Box 32)
  - Forestry (Box 33)
  - Forestry Pulpwood Meeting, 1948 June (Box 33)
  - Forestry Science Research Lab (Box 33)
  - Former Employees (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Forum on Presidential Nominations, 1972 (Box 33)
  - Founder's Day, to 1965 (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Founder's Day, 1966 (Box 33)
  - Fraternities, 1957-1971 (Box 33)
  - French, 1944-1969 (Box 33)
  - Freshman (Box 33)
  - Freshman Advisory Program (Box 33)
  - Fritz London Memorial Lecture, 1970- (Box 33)
  - Geology, 1975 (Box 33)
  - Geology (Box 33)
  - Germanic Languages (Box 33)
  - Gifts, 1974-1976 (Box 33)
  - Glee Club, 1947-1958 (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Glee Club, 1959-1965 (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Glee Club, 1966- (Box 34)
  - Governance Commission, University, 1970 (Box 34)
  - Graduate School (Box 34)
  - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences, 1938-1965 (Box 34)
  - Grants, 1956-1963 (Box 34)
  - Grants, 1964-1966 (Box 34)
  - Grants, 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Grants, 1968-1974 (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Grants, 1971-1973 (Box 34)
  - Greek (Box 34)
  - Guidance Counselor High School (Box 34)
  - Health Fair (Box 34)
  - Highlands Biological Station (Box 34)
  - History (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Homecoming, 1948-1961 (Box 35)
  - Homecoming, 1958-1965 (Box 35)
  - Homecoming, 1966-1974 (Box 35)
  - Honorary Degree Recipients (Box 35)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn, to 1967 (Box 35)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn, 1968- (Box 35)
  - House Counselors (Box 35)
  - Housing (Box 35)
  - Humanities Coop Program (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Humphrey Visit, 1965 (Box 35)
  - Institute of Policy Studies & Public Affairs (Box 35)
  - Integration/Segregation, 1960-1963 (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Integration/Segregation, 1964-1971 (Box 36)
  - International Affairs Week (Box 36)
  - International Lecture Center, 1978 (Box 36)
  - International Studies Program (Box 36)
  - Internship Programs, to 1977 (Box 36)
  - Joe College Days (Box 36)
  - Judaic Studies (Box 36)
  - Junior Science Program (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1958, 1959, 1971 (Box 36)
  - Kearns Foundation for Graduate Study in Religion, 1961 (Box 36)
  - Labor Law Institute, 1949 (Box 36)
  - Lamar Society, L.Q.C. (Box 36)
  - Law (Box 36)
  - Law Day, 1962-1971 (Box 36)
  - Law Day, 1971-1974 (Box 36)
  - Law Forum, 1968-1975 (Box 36)
  - Law School, 1943-1952 (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Law School, 1952-1959 (1 of 2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Law School, 1952-1959 (2 of 2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1959-1962 (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1963-1964 (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1966-1967 (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1968-1973 (Box 37)
  - Law School Pictures (Box 37)
  - Law School (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1970-1976 (Box 37)
  - Law School, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Law School, 1974 (Box 38)
  - Law School, 1975-1977 (Box 38)
  - Law School, 1977-1984 (Box 38)
  - Learning Institute of North Carolina (Box 38)
  - Lectures, 1964-1974 (Box 38)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1974-1976 (Box 38)
  - Lectures Basset, John Spencer Memorial Series (Box 38)
  - Lectures Duke, Benjamin N. (Box 38)
  - Lectures Gray, James A. (Box 38)
  - Lectures Hart, Deryl, 1971 (Box 38)
  - Lectures Hickman, Frank S. Memorial (Box 38)
  - Lectures Lilly Series Christianity and Politics (Box 38)
  - Lectures London, Fritz Memorial [See also Sigma Xi File] (Box 38)
  - Lectures Sweaney, Dr. Hunter Surgery (Box 38)
  - Lectures Trent Memorial (Box 38)
  - Library, 1938-1949 (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Library, 1950-1959 (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Library, 1959-1964 (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Library, 1965-1967 (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Library, 1968-1970 (3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Library, 1971-1974 (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Literary Festival, Blackburn Formerly Archive Festival (Box 40)
  - Long Range Planning (Box 40)
  - Loyalty Fund, to 1958 (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Loyalty Fund, 1959-1962 (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Loyalty Fund, 1963-1970 (Box 40)
  - Madrigal Singers (Box 40)
  - Malcom X University and related articles (Box 40)
  - Marine Lab (3 of 9 folders) (Box 40)
  - Marine Lab (6 of 9 folders) (Box 41)
  - Mathematics (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1943 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1946 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1947 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1948 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1949 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1950 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1951 (Box 41)
  - Math Institute, 1952 (Box 41)
  - Mazzoni Library (Box 41)
  - Men's Student Government, 1950-1965 (Box 42)
  - Methodist Church (Box 42)
  - Methodist Judicial Council (Box 42)
  - Methodist Laymen (Box 42)
  - Methodist School of Missions (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Methodist Seminar, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Methodist Student Activities (Box 42)
  - Methodist Youth Fellowship, 1953-1967 (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous (3 folders) (Box 42)
  - Missions Emphasis Week (Box 42)
  - Missions Symposium (Box 42)
  - Modern Dance (Box 42)
  - Monitor, 1973 (Box 42)
  - Monitor, 1974 (3 of 7 folders) (Box 42)
  - Monitor, 1974 (4 of 7 folders) (Box 43)
  - Monitor, 1975 (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Monitor, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Monitor, 1977 (Box 43)
  - Monitor, 1978 (Box 43)
  - Monitor, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Monitor, 1986 (Box 43)
  - Mother Parent Daughter Weekend (Box 43)
  - Municipal and Industrial Waste Conference (Box 43)
  - Music, 1960-1963 (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Music, 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Music, 1966-1973 (3 folders) (Box 44)
  - Music, 1973-1974 (Box 44)
  - Music, 1975 (Box 44)
  - Music Department, 1976 (Box 44)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 44)
  - National Council (Box 44)
  - National Driving Center, 1973 (Box 44)
  - National Emergency College Program (Box 44)
  - National Humanities Center, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
  - National Laborator for Higher Education, 1971-1973 (Box 44)
  - National Merit Scholarships (Box 44)
  - National Resources Conference (Box 44)
  - National Security Seminar (Box 44)
  - National Teachers' Examination, 1973 (Box 44)
  - Naval R.O.T.C., 1941-1976 (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Naval R.O.T.C., 1942-1966 (2 of 3 folders) (Box 44)
  - Naval R.O.T.C., 1942-1966 (3 of 3 folders) (Box 45)
  - Naval Research Unit (Box 45)
  - New York Times and National Magazine Clippings, pre-1966 (Box 45)
  - North Carolina Academy of Science (Box 45)
  - North Carolina Council of Churches (Box 45)
  - North Carolina Fund Including Linc-Learning Institute of NC Also N.C. Volunteers (Box 45)
  - N.C. Institute of Politics, 1973 (Box 45)
  - North Carolina Regional Medical Program (Box 45)
  - Nuclear Research Project (Box 45)
  - Nursery School (Box 45)
  - Nursing Institute (Box 45)
  - Oak Ridge (3 folders) (Box 45)
  - Office of Information Services (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Operation Breakthrough (Box 45)
  - Orientation 1948-1964 (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Organ and Organ Recitals, 1949-1969 (Box 46)
  - Ormond Center, 1970 (Box 46)
  - Orphanage Workers, 1937 (Box 46)
  - Parapsychology and FRNM, 1961-1973 (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Parapsychology, 1964-1967 (Box 46)
  - Parapsychology, 1968-1974 (Box 46)
  - Parapsychology, 1975-1976 (Box 46)
  - Parapsychology Lab (see also J. B. Rhine) (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Parent's Weekend (Box 46)
  - Pastors' School and Convocation, 1949-1969 (Box 46)
  - Pastors' School, 1939-1975 (Box 47)
  - Paths for Employee Progress PEP (Box 47)
  - Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 47)
  - Personnel Non-Academic, 1962-1974 (Box 47)
  - Personnel Conference, 1947-1953 (Box 47)
  - Personnel Conference, 1954-1957 (Box 47)
  - Personnel Conference, 1968-1974 (Box 47)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Philosophy, 1948-1975 (Box 47)
  - Physical Planning, 1968 (Box 47)
  - Physical Education (Box 47)
  - Physical Education, 1951-1975 (Box 47)
  - Physics, 1939-1959 (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Physics, 1959-1965 (Box 47)
  - Physics, 1966-1974 See also Nuclear Structure (Box 47)
  - Physics, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Phytotron (Box 48)
  - Pie Throwing Incident, 1975 (Box 48)
  - Placements, 1962-1966 (Box 48)
  - Placement Office (Box 48)
  - Political Activities (Box 48)
  - Political Science, 1939-1966 (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - Political Science, 1966-1975 (Box 48)
  - Political Science, 1975 (Box 48)
  - Political Science Meeting, 1950 (Box 48)
  - Pollution and Environment (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - Population Control (Box 48)
  - Postgraduate Medical Course, 1950-1961 (Box 48)
  - Premature Infant Care Program (Box 48)
  - Presbyterian Student Center (Box 48)